templatekingdom.com 2012-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Template Kingdom

Template Kingdom (hereafter referred to as Template Kingdom) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. 

### Coverage & Scope

  * This privacy policy covers Template Kingdom's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by Template Kingdom, a website owned and operated by Template Kingdom. 
  * This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Template Kingdom does not own or control, or of persons that Template Kingdom does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Template Kingdom websites link.

### How we collect and use your personal information

  * You can visit the websites of Template Kingdom without revealing any personal information. However, Template Kingdom needs certain personal information if you wish to sign up for our membership, purchase our products or service, register for an affiliate account, receive our newsletter, or use certain services offered by Template Kingdom.
  * Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. Template Kingdom will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member's account, and to contact you regarding new products and services.
  * By accessing the services of Template Kingdom and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### How we collect and use your non-personal information

  * Template Kingdom automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. Template Kingdom may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, Template Kingdom does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.
  * Template Kingdom also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their privacy policies, and Template Kingdom assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.

### How we share and disclose your data

  * Template Kingdom may otherwise disclose your personal information when: 
    * We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;
    * We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;
    * We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Template Kingdom;
    * We find that your actions on our websites violate the Template Kingdom Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

### Consent

  * If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to Template Kingdom. If you have provided personal information to Template Kingdom and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify Template Kingdom at privacy@templatekingdom.com

### Security of your data

  * Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your Template Kingdom Information protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, Template Kingdom uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
  * We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.
  * Further, Template Kingdom retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by law.

### Changes

  * Template Kingdom may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of Template Kingdom websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

### Contacting us regarding our privacy policy

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at [privacy@templatekingdom.com](http://www.cloudflare.com/email-protection#b7c7c5dec1d6d4cef7c3d2dac7dbd6c3d2dcded9d0d3d8da99d4d8da)
